dianeestrella.com 2016-10-12

# Privacy Policy - Diane Estrella

Diane Estrella (" **Diane Estrella** ") operates dianeestrella.com and may operate other websites. It is Diane Estrella's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Diane Estrella collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Diane Estrella's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Diane Estrella's visitors use its website. From time to time, Diane Estrella may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Diane Estrella also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on dianeestrella.com blogs/sites. Diane Estrella only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Diane Estrella's websites choose to interact with Diane Estrella in ways that require Diane Estrella to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Diane Estrella gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at [dianeestrella.com](http://dianeestrella.com/) to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Diane Estrella are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Diane Estrella collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Diane Estrella. Diane Estrella does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

Diane Estrella may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Diane Estrella may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Diane Estrella does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Diane Estrella discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Diane Estrella's behalf or to provide services available at Diane Estrella's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Diane Estrella's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Diane Estrella will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Diane Estrella discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Diane Estrella believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Diane Estrella, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Diane Estrella website and have supplied your email address, Diane Estrella may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Diane Estrella and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Diane Estrella takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Diane Estrella uses cookies to help Diane Estrella identify and track visitors, their usage of Diane Estrella website, and their website access preferences. Diane Estrella visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Diane Estrella's websites, with the drawback that certain features of Diane Estrella's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

If Diane Estrella, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Diane Estrella goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Diane Estrella may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Diane Estrella and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Diane Estrella may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Diane Estrella's sole discretion. Diane Estrella encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a dianeestrella.com account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
